sociolla.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Sociolla

Welcome to www.sociolla.com (“Sociolla” or “Site”). We respect the privacy of your personal information. Please read the information contained on this page as our guidance (“Privacy Policy”). We do not share or disclose any of your personal information to third parties except in the case where it is part of providing a service to you, for example, delivery address for your purchased items as well as credit and other security checks. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, protect, and in some cases, disclose your personal information. By visiting this Site, you agree and accept the terms described in this Policy.

### **COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Sociolla requests information that is deemed to be necessary and important in order for us to ensure accurate and satisfactory service. All of the information we collect is basic and is required to complete a purchase or provide a refund. Sociolla requests various information including, but not limited to, your full name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, bank account information, and descriptions of the items requested or purchased.

### **NAVIGATION INFORMATION  
**

Sociolla has and utilizes our ability to track usage of our web site, including visited pages, what products are viewed, and the third-party sites that led you to Sociolla. This information is not used to track information about individuals, but is used at an aggregate level to customize our site, improve the online experience, and plan advertising and promotions.

### **INFORMATION VOLUNTARILY PROVIDED**

All information that you input and provide to Sociolla is voluntary. This occurs when you provide feedback to us through e-mails, return forms, letters, or telephone calls. We use this information to respond to your query, to keep track of customer feedback, and to improve our service to customers.

### **INTERNET DATABASE**

Sociolla has created an Internet database to allow customers to store their shipping and billing information, payment preferences, track the status of their order, credit card information, list previous orders, email preferences as well as certain personal information in regards to own physical characteristics. Any forms of registrations including our membership program (“Beauty Clique”) as well as our newsletter are voluntary, and you have the ability to correct or delete the information at any time. This information can be accessed through the “My Account” section of the site.

### **ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Sociolla is committed to ensure that we have no personal information about customers that is a prerequisite to provide them with excellent service. We are committed to ensure that information about our customers is accurate and up-to-date.

### **MARKETING INFORMATION**

Sociolla respects your information and does not sell or otherwise share your personal information with anyone else, such as advertising agencies or marketing companies.

### **DISCLOSURE AND RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Sociolla will share your personal information internally with our staff members who need them in order to complete your purchases or carry out your instructions regarding the receipt of marketing information. Authorized Sociolla service providers may also have access to this information to carry out their responsibilities directly connected with the processing of your purchases or handling of customer service issues.

Sociolla keeps your personal information for only as long as required to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected. In some cases, such as credit- or debit-card purchases, we are required by law to keep your personal information for a specified period of time. For those customers who have registered for the mailing list, their personal information is kept until we are notified that they no longer want their information stored.

Sociolla, as with many other web sites, makes use of "cookies" to help deliver a better customer shopping experience. Cookies are alphanumerical identification elements that we transfer to the hard drive of your computer via your web browser. They enable our systems to recognize your browser and to offer you valuable services, such as saving the contents of your shopping basket, to allow you to access your account information, and to deliver a more personalized shopping experience.

### **ACCURACY AND PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Sociolla relies on our customers to notify us of any changes in personal information. Should inaccurate information come to our attention, we will investigate and correct the information and, if necessary, advise you of the change. Only those staff members who need your personal information in order to respond to your requests are given access to it. All information stored in our computer system is protected from unauthorized access, and information that is stored in document form is kept in secure locations to prevent access by unauthorized persons.

### TRANSACTION SECURITY

In order to make every effort to ensure that your experience at www.Sociolla.com is secure, we use encryption technology to protect you against the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. When you fill out any contact forms or access your account, a secure server encrypts all of your information through the use of Secure Socket Layers (SSLs).

**Should you wish to learn about information we have about you, please send emails to:[info@Sociolla.com](mailto:info@Sociolla.com)**
